Hello.
喂
Wanna have a little fun?
想找乐子吗
Who's this?
你是谁
Tell me your name and I'll tell you mine.
你先说你的吧
I don't think so.
我才不要
What's that noise?
什么声音
Oops. I farted.
我放屁了
I didn't think you would hear me.
没想到你听得见
No, that popping noise.
不 那噗噗的声音
Oh. I'm making popcorn.
我在做爆米花
I'm getting ready to watch a video.
准备看片子
Ooh. What is it?
什么片子
It's just a scary movie.
只是部恐怖片
- Do you like scary movies?   - Mm-hmm.
- 你喜欢恐怖片吗  - 嗯
What's your favorite?
你最喜欢哪一部
Mm, I don't know.
不知道
Think.
想想嘛
Oh, I know. Um, Kazaam,
有了 是精灵也疯狂
the one where Shaq plays a genie.
侠客欧尼尔演精灵的那一部
That's not a horror movie.
那不是恐怖片
Well, you haven't seen Shaq act.
那是你没看过欧尼尔的演技
Hey, you have a nice voice.
你的声音很甜美
Thanks.
谢了
You never did tell me your name.
你没告诉我你是谁
Why do you wanna know my name?
你为何想知道
Cause I wanna know who I'm looking at.
我想知道我现在正在看的是谁
What... What did you say?
你说什么
Nice breasts.
大波霸
Look, what do you want?
你想干嘛
I wanna see what your insides look like.
我想看看你里面有没有料
Well... Well, then, turn to page 54.
那就翻到55页
Hey, nice.
好耶
Listen, asshole, you've had your fun,
混球 你闹够了
now you better stop or else.
你最好就此打住
Or else what?
不然呢
Or else my boyfriend's gonna be here any minute,
我男友随时会到
and he's black and he'll kick your ass.
他是黑人 可以扁死你
Oh, really?
是吗
Yeah.
对
You mean the one who wears makeup and dresses like a woman?
你是指打扮成女人的那个
How did you know?
你怎么知道
Turn the porch lights on.
把阳台的灯打开
Help! Help!
救命 救命
Oh, that's not my boyfriend.
不是他啦
I mean, I've fucked him a couple of times, but that's it.
我不过就跟他上过几次床而已
Look, I'm calling the cops.
我要报警了
Go ahead. Call the cops.
去啊 去报警啊
But you might wanna check the back door first.
但你最好先查看一下后门
You forgot to lock it.
你忘了上锁了
Take that, you psycho!
接招吧 大变态
I can't feel my legs.
我的脚没知觉了
I think my arm is broken.
我的手断了
Sorry.
抱歉
I want my mommy.
我要跟我妈讲
Hello, Drew.
你好 茱儿
Oh, God!
天啊
(活路 死路)
No
不
Daddy!
爸
Daddy, no! No!
爸 不 不
Did you hear something?
什么声音
No, I didn't hear anything.
我没听见什么声音
《惊声尖笑》
Bobby, what are you doing?
巴比 你干嘛
My dad's in the other room.
我爸就在隔壁
It just occurred to me.
我想起
I never climbed through your window before.
我从未从窗户爬进来过
Now that you got it out of your system,
现在你满足了吧
Bobby, you have to leave.
你快走吧
Why?
为什么
Shh. Come on.
小心
What's going on in there?
里面怎么了
Ow! Daddy's head is stuck.
老爸的头卡住了
Unstick Daddy's head.
快松开
Dad, can you knock?
爸 拜托你先敲门嘛
Knock?
敲门
I thought I heard screaming in here.
我听见里面有人尖叫
No. No, you didn't, Dad.
没有人尖叫啊
Well, it could've been that crack I smoked earlier, I guess.
可能是我刚嗑药的幻觉吧
Yeah, that's what it was.
没错
Listen, I gotta leave town for a couple of days. O.K?
我要离开镇上几天
No big deal.
别担心
Just that new business I started with those Colombian guys?
我跟那几个哥伦比亚人的生意
Oh, you mean Uncle Escobar.
你是说艾斯可叔叔
Yeah. Yeah, that's right.
对
Well, there's a problem.
出了问题
Some money went missing.
有些钱不见了
And apparently, some legs are gonna get broken.
看来有些人会完了
It's just better if I lay low for a couple of days.
我最好还是躲个几天吧
If the cops raid the place...
如果警察来查
I never heard of you.
我根本不认识你
And don't forget...
别忘了
To flush your stash.
湮灭证据
Oh, you are my little girl.
你真棒
I love you so much...
我爱你
that I left you a little something in the coffee can.
我在咖啡罐里留了点好料给你
- Dad...   - But you have to remember to step on it before you sell it.
- 爸爸  - 卖之前记得要掺点料
Now, what are you gonna cut it with?
你要拿什么掺进去
Um, baking...
苏打
Baking soda. Not baking powder.
苏打粉不是发粉
Because baking powder
放发粉
guys will have muffins growing out of their nose.
帅哥就会发了
You love that joke, don't you, honey?
你就喜欢这样 对吧
You've loved that joke since you were two years old.
你两岁时就喜欢这样掺了
Okay, well...
好吧
Okay, I love you.
我爱你
I love you.
Have a good trip.
一路顺风
- Bye.   - Bye.
- 拜  - 拜
Is the coast clear?
安全了
Oh, Cindy, that nightgown.
辛蒂这件睡衣
That was close. God!
真惊险 天啊
I was, uh, home watching The Exorcist,
我本来在家看大法师
and it got me thinking about you.
那片子却让我想起你
If this is about the time I puked green slime
若你是想起我吐绿黏液
and masturbated with a crucifix...
还用十字架自慰的那次
It was my first keg party, Bobby.
那是我第一次参加饮酒大会
No. No.
不 不
Uh, it was edited for TV.
那是电视版
All the good stuff was cut out.
精彩片段都剪了
So you thought you would just climb through my window...
那你是想爬上来
and we would play bump-bump?
跟我玩耍
I was kind of hoping to get my balls licked,
我是希望有人能舔我蛋蛋
but I wouldn't wanna break your little underwear rule,
但我决不会动你内裤
now, would I?
好吗
So maybe just some on-top-of-the-clothes type stuff?
也许我能跟你隔着睡衣玩玩
Okay. But just for a minute.
好吧 就一下子
What the...
搞什么
Wrong set.
跑错场景了
Bobby!
巴比
Oh, Bobby!
No, Bobby, don't.
巴比 不要
Jeez.
天啊
(禁止入内)
Yeah, my dad.
是我爸
Okay, stud, you have to go now.
好了 大种马 你该走了
Oh, um, about the sex stuff?
关于上床的事
I was only half serious. I don't wanna rush you or anything.
我并不想逼你
Hey, would you settle for PG-13?
你接受辅导级的画面吗
What's that?
什么
Oh, jeez!
天啊
Good night, Bobby.
晚安 巴比
Shorty, you are so loud.
矮子你好吵
And make sure you take your behind to class today.
记得今天要去上课
I do be going to class.
我会去上课的
Lunch is not a class, Shorty.
吃便当不叫上课
It is when you got the munchies.
偷吃零食总算吧
See, that's why you such a dumb-ass.
看吧 你就是这么蠢
Your mother.
去你妈的
You my brother. That's your mother too, jackass.
你是我弟 那也是你妈
Oh, yeah.
对喔
Well, then, your father's stupid.
那你爸是猪头
So? I don't know him.
又怎样 我又不知他是谁
Yeah, me neither.
是啊 我也是
Hey, girl, you ready?
辣妹 准备好了
Yeah, in a minute.
一会就好
We're gonna be late.
快点 我们迟到了
Wait. There's Buffy.
等等 帕妃来了
I don't know why you hang out with her.
你干嘛跟她混
She is such a ho.
她是个贱货
Why do you say that?
你干嘛这样说
Cause I've seen her.
因为我知道
My friend Sean had a pool party this summer.
我朋友小席夏天开了泳池派对
Sean?
小席
You know, Puff Daddy?
你知道的 吹牛老爹
Anyway, everybody was drinking Cristal champagne.
大家都在喝法国香槟
And then it started to get wild,
接着大家都发疯
and people were getting freaky in the pool and stuff.
在池里乱搞
I look over and there was your girl getting buck wild in theJacuzzi.
我看到 她在按摩池跟男人乱搞
So?
那又怎样
With a backup dancer.
对方是个伴舞的
I mean, that's nasty.
那真是没格调
That's, That's lower than the security guard.
那比跟警卫搞还没品
At least security can get you backstage.
至少警卫能放你进场看演唱会
She don't love herself.
她真不自爱
I don't know.
我不知道
I think Buffy's sweet, Brenda.
我觉得帕妃很甜美
She is as fake as Press-on nails.
她假仙死了
Hey, baby girl!
嘿 小甜甜
What is up, my sister?
你好 好姊妹
- Bye, Mr. Gilmore.   - Bye!
- 拜 吉先生  - 拜
- Is he gone?   - Yep.
- 他走了  - 对
Hey, Cindy!
嗨 辛蒂
I love this color.
我喜欢这个颜色
Let me see that.
让我看看
Oh, you guys should not use this brand.
你们不该用这个牌子
Why not?
为什么
Because they test their products on animals.
他们拿产品在动物身上试验
So?
所以呢
Look, have you seen what they do to those poor animals?
看过他们怎么对待那些动物吗
(停止动物试验)
Well, I am much more of a people person.
我很关心大众
I'd like to feed all the hungry, little children of the world.
我愿意接济世上饥贫的孩童
I'd much rather help my fellow man than some animal.
我宁可帮助人
Spare a dollar?
给我一元吧
Get away from me, you bum!
滚远一点脏鬼
Buffy! Can't you see he's just hungry?
他只是饿了
Here you go, sir. A nice sandwich.
拿去吧 这是三明治
See?
看到了吧
I said a dollar, bitch!
我要的是一元
God. Look at this place.
天啊 看看这地方
It's a circus.
真像马戏团大公演
Hello. I'm Gail Hailstorm,
你们好 我是海盖儿
author of the book, You're Dead, I'm Rich.
畅销书《你死我赚》的作者
A small college town is in shock...
一个小镇因一椿事故
after the unthinkable has happened:
陷入恐慌
A brutal killing spree that left one teen dead...
一位少女惨遭残酷谋杀
That's it.
我受够了
Two teens dead...
两位青少年死亡
And this small town shaken and stirred.
这个小镇陷入混乱中
It's times like these...
这种时刻
Police are combing the area for clues.
警方到处寻找线索
There are no witnesses available at this time.
目前并未找到目击证人
There are no suspects in custody.
也没有逮捕嫌疑犯
Police are asking anyone to come forward.
警方请求民众协助破案
Reporting live for Black TV.
黑人电台为您报导
White folks are dead and we're getting the fuck out of here!
白人死了 我们快走
Grab your shit and let's go, motherfucker!
快落跑啊 妈的快收拾好走啊
Hey, do you think the press is gonna wanna talk to us?
你想媒体会访问我们吗
Oh, girl, no.
不
The press only wants to interview the most ignorant person they can find.
媒体只想访问最无知的人
I'm on TV!
我上电视了
Oh, shit! First Cops, now this!
上回是被捕时上的
Oh, man, I'm gonna be a star, son!
天啊 我会变成名人的
What can you tell us about Drew?
请你谈谈遇害的茱儿
Well, she had the phat ass.
她的屁股真大
I mean, it was like bang!
大辣妹
How close were you to the victim?
你跟她熟吗
Real close.
很熟
Until the roofies wore off.
强暴丸药效过后
Then she woke up talking about pressing charges.
她说要告我
So I just pulled my tongue out of her ass and left.
所以我就不继续舔她屁屁了
What would have been your last words to Drew?
你想对茱儿说什么
Run, bitch! Run!
跑 贱货快跑啊
Hey, yo, dawg. Does this shirt make me look gay?
兄弟 我这样穿像同志吗
No, man.
不像
What about now?
现在呢
- Nah.   - Cool?
- 不像  - 酷吗
Yeah.
很好
Here. Take one, guys.
拿一张吧
Don't forget: Election's Tuesday.
别忘了周二投票
Ah! Goddamn it! Son of a bitch!
该死 他妈的旦旦面
What's the matter, honey?
怎么了 宝贝
My report card.
我的成绩单
Well, at least you got one "A."
白痴 至少里面还有个A嘛
Yeah. I did, huh?
对喔 没错
You're so smart.
你真聪明
Hey, has anybody seen Bobby?
有看到巴比吗
Nah.
没有
You know what? That kid is always late.
那家伙老爱迟到
I don't get it. He lives so close.
我真不懂 他住的那么近
See you later, Hairy Mama, Bubba, Jim,
回头见了 老爸 老妈 吉姆
BigJim, LittleJim, Slim Jim, everybody.
大小吉姆瘦吉姆 还有大家
I'll see you later. Ciao, Ding. All right.
拜了 小弟回头见
Damn, girl.
辣妹
I'd sure like to get in them pants.
我真想钻进你裤裆里
Really?
真的
Yeah. What size are these?
是啊 你穿几号的裤子
Hey, guys.
大家好
- Hey, Bobby.   - Hey, baby.
- 嗨 巴比  - 宝贝
- How you doing?   - Good.
- 你好吗  - 很好
You guys see all the reporters out there?
有看到那些记者吗
Yeah.
听说了
Saying that girl Drew Decker got killed last night.
听说辣妹茱儿昨晚被人杀了
You know what? I think I knew her.
我想我认识她
Really?
真的
She had a brother named Steve?
对 她哥叫史提夫吧
Yeah.
没错
Long hair, pretty little mouth, perfect ass?
留长发 樱桃小嘴 俏屁股
That was her.
是她没错
Nah, I was talking about Steve.
不 我说的是史提夫
Whatever happened to him?
他到底发生什么事了
Do you guys think it's strange that she got killed...
你们觉得她在整整一年后
exactly one year after we,
被人谋杀
you know, killed that guy?
跟我们杀了那人 有关系吗
Hey, Cindy, that was an accident.
那是意外
Was it, Greg?
是吗 格瑞
Would you look at what they're doing?
你看他们在搞什么鬼
When are we gonna do stuff like that, huh?
我们何时才能做那档事
One day.
总有一天吧
- You like that, baby?   - Yeah, that's different.
- 你喜欢吗  - 喜欢 真特别
- You like that?   - Oh, I love that.
- 你喜欢  - 我爽透了
Oh, I love when you play with my ass.
我喜欢你摸我屁屁
I'm not playing with your ass.
我没摸你屁屁
Ray!
小雷
Oh, my bad.
我弄错了
Come on, man!
拜托
Hey, Bobby, put on some music.
巴比 放点音乐吧
Hold on.
等等
Here. Put this on.
放这卷
Yeah, that's the shit right here!
真是棒呆了
Baby.
宝贝
Stop!
停
What?
怎么
Well, it's classic.
这很经典呢
Put on the radio, man.
听收音机吧
- What! It was laundry day.   - What the fuck is...
- 怎么 那是我妈的  - 搞什么
Hey. Come over here.
过来
What?
干嘛
Just get a little closer to me.
再靠近一点
Something you're gonna tell me?
你想跟我说什么
Bobby, what are you doing?
你干嘛
I just want you to touch it. Just touch it. Come on.
我只要你摸摸它 拜托
Just a little bit. Come on.
摸一下就好
Oh, yeah, that's what I'm talkin' about.
我就想要你这样
Oh, my God!
爽啊
Yeah, Cindy...
辛蒂
oh, shit!
糟糕
Oh, my God.
我的老天
What was that?
怎么回事
I think we hit something.
我想我们撞到东西了
Oh, man!
天啊
Bobby, look at my car, man! My dad's gonna freak!
你看车子撞的 我爸会发飙的
I didn't see it. It came out of nowhere.
我没看到 它突然钻出来的
Oh, my God, we hit a boot.
天啊 我们撞上一只靴子
Where's the foot?
脚呢
I don't know.
不知道
Where the...
搞什么
It's a body!
尸体在那
Oh, shit, is he alive?
妈的 他死了
I don't know.
不知道
- Well, check it out.   - I can't.
- 去看一下  - 我不要
- Shit!   - We have to call the police.
- 妈的  - 我们得报警
No way. I ain't going to jail.
不行 我不要坐牢
We have to!
一定得报警
Hey, Cindy, do you know what they do to young boys in prison?
知道少男被送进牢会怎样吗
And all those sex-starved convicts just waiting for a fresh piece of meat.
那些性饥渴的囚犯就等着你
Hey, you're right, Cindy. Maybe we should call the police.
也许我们该报警
Oh, yeah, That's a great idea, Ray.
真好啊 小雷
But what about Brenda, huh?
布兰妲呢
You think she wants to go to jail?
你以为她想坐牢
This is manslaughter, okay?
这是过失杀人
We're all gonna fry for this.
我们死定了
We're looking at 10 to 15 years.
等着被关十到十五年吧
Shut up, Bobby!
闭嘴 巴比
- It's okay. I'm fine.   - We're in so much trouble.
- 我没事  - 麻烦大了
I'm fine.
我没事
Don't blamethat shit on me, Ray.
别想把责任推给我
Look, we'll get rid of the body.
天啊 我们得毁尸灭迹
Unnecessary.
不需要
Now you're thinking.
你终于动脑袋了
- We'll dump him in the ocean.   - Not the ocean, the pier.
- 把他丢进海里  - 丢码头边
Guess I'll be leaving now.
我马上走
That's a great idea.
好主意
- What about the alcohol?   - We'll get rid of it.
- 酒呢  - 丢了它
Come on. It'll be all right.
不会有问题的
Come on. Hurry up. Let's go.
没错 动手吧
Put him in the trunk.
把他塞进后车厢
I won't have anything to do with this!
我不想跟这件事有关连
Shut up!
闭嘴
Cindy, come on. We'lljust pretend it never happened.
辛蒂 拜托 我们就假装什么都没发生过
You know, like the time we got drunk
就像我们喝醉
and we went down on each other.
乱搞那次一样
I'll get his arm.
我抓他的手
- l'll grab his other arm.   - l'll grab his his ass.
- 我抓其他只手  - 我抓他屁屁
We'll take him down to Williamson Cove and we'll dump him in there.
我们把他丢到威森湾里
The sharks'll take care of the evidence.
鲨鱼会帮我们料理他
Oh, my God, someone's coming.
天啊 有人来了
Oh, shit. It's Shorty.
该死是矮子
Brenda, take care of him.
布兰妲 搞定他
Shorty, I know you ain't driving without no papers.
矮子 你一定是无照驾驶
I got papers, blunts, bongs,
我有 我罩子亮着呢
all the ingredients to make a high nigga pie.
还有令人精神振奋的好料
Hey, yo, can I help you?
你在这干嘛
Yo, what's up, Ray?
小雷啊
Yo, son, you all need jumper cables?
需要接电吗
Nah, we're cool.
不 不用
Oh, good, 'cause I left my roach clip at home.
很好 反正我也没带
Go home, Shorty.
回家去 矮子
Yeah, I-I'll see you later.
回头见
Peace, Ray.
拜了 小雷
Get the trunk closed.
把后车厢关上
It won't close.
关不起来
I'll do it.
我来
Hold on. Hold on. Put him down.
拜托 等等把他放下
He's heavy. Oh, God.
他真重 天啊
Okay, look. On three we dump him over the ledge.
好听着 数到三就把他丢下去
Wait, wait, wait. Shouldn't we at least check his wallet?
等等 检查一下他的皮夹吧
For what?
干嘛
Shit, he might have some money.
他也许有钱呢
We already committed murder.
我们已杀了他
We might as well rob his ass.
就顺便抢他吧
I'll take the credit cards.
我拿信用卡
I want his jewelry.
我要珠宝
I'm gonna take his drawers.
我要他的内裤
Get off! Hey, yo, get off! His drawers are mine! Yo!
放手 他的内裤是我的
- I got me a gold ring.   - Credit cards.
- 我拿到金戒指了  - 信用卡
All right, let's get him in the water.
把他丢进水里吧
I don't think I can, Greg.
我做不到
It's not too late.
现在还不迟
Shut up, okay?
闭嘴 好吗
Christ, already. I'll do it.
天啊 我动手
Just get him in the water. O.K?
把他丢进水里就好 好吗
One, two,
一 二
three.
三
Right now we make a pact.
现在我们达成协议
We take this to our grave.
一辈子都谨守秘密
- Agreed?   - Agreed.
- 同意  - 同意
Say it, Cindy.
说啊 辛蒂
Say it!
说啊
We take this to our grave. Say it!
一辈子谨守秘密 说啊
We take this to our grave. Say it.
一辈子都谨守秘密 说啊
Greg, chill. Come on. You're hurting her.
说啊 格瑞 冷静
We take this to our grave. Ow.
一辈子谨守秘密格瑞
And we never mention this again.
我们绝口不提
Mention what?
不提什么
The guy we just killed.
我们刚杀了一个人
Well, you just mentioned it, Greg.
你刚刚就提了
Starting now!
从现在开始算
Stupid bitch, man.
真是个蠢妞
God. I hate him.
我恨他
It's gonna be okay, baby.
不会有事的宝贝
It's gonna be okay.
不会有事的
I promise. Just touch it again.
我保证 再摸一次
Come on. Please.
拜托
You have to move on, Cindy.
你要向前看 辛蒂
That's all behind us now.
一切都过去了
Exactly. It's a coincidence.
没错 这是巧合
Greg's right, Cindy.
格瑞说的对
I mean, what do you think we're in, a horror movie?
你以为我们在演恐怖片吗
Yeah, you guys are right. If we were,
你们说的对 如果是的话
they'd probably cast some dingbat
也许演我的人
like Jennifer Love Huge Tits to play me.
会是个大波霸
Yeah, or they'd cast people in their late twenties,
也许会找三十岁的
early thirties to play us.
老演员来演
Kenny, get the camera ready. Here. Hold my gum.
摄影机准备 把我口香糖收好
Sheriff, Sheriff, can I get a statement?
警长 请您讲几句话
No comment.
无可奉告
Damn.
该死
Who do I have to screw around here to get a stupid story?
我跟谁搞才弄得到内幕消息
Hey! Hey, no running.
别乱跑
Loser.
笨蛋
Slow it down!
慢慢走
Blow me!
咬我啊
All right!
好吧
Hi. Gail Hailstorm. Field Reporter, Hard Story.
我是新闻前线采访记者 海盖儿
Special officer Doofy.
特别警探阿呆
Oh, hi, Doofy.
你好 阿呆
Doofy, listen. Is there a problem on campus?
阿呆 校园里出了什么事
- No comment.   - Okay.
- 无可奉告  - 好吧
You know, you look awfully young to be a police officer.
你真是个年轻有为的警探
I'm 25 and a half years old.
我二十五岁半了
Yeah, that's this many.
就这么大
Ah, so big.
真大
Yeah. That's big.
对 很大了
Well, you don't look a day over 12.
你看来不过才十二岁
Except for the big head and glazed-over look in your eyes.
但你的眼神可锐利了
Ooh, was that drool?
那是口水吗
Yeah. I forgot to swallow.
对 我忘了吞下去了
Don't worry, cause I never forget.
不用担心 我不会忘的
Would you remind me not to do that again?
提醒我别再搔你了
Sorry.
抱歉
Due to the recent tragedy, the sheriff and me, your principal,
针对这场悲剧 警长和我
will be questioning all students throughout the day.
会开始询问所有的学生
Wow. Sounds like we've got the makings of
看来似乎是有个
a serial killer on our hands.
连续杀人犯
Yeah, I'm not supposed to say.
我不能说
It's official police business.
这是警方事务
Hey, Doofy, what do you say you and I
阿呆 你和我
go inside my van over there...
一起去车里
and, uh, get to know each other a little better?
互相认识一下吧
Would you like that?
怎么样
- That van?   - Yeah, that van right there.
- 车里  - 对 就是那辆车
Yeah, Yeah, okay, let's go.
好吧 我们走
Come on.
走吧
Aterrible tragedy and an unbearable loss.
这真是桩可怕的悲剧
It's days like today that we need prayer in school.
在这样的日子里 我们需要祷告
It starts to unravel the very moral fabric of our society.
它已侵蚀我们的信念
Here you go, baby.
好了
Go to your daddy.
去找你爸吧
I'll see you after class.
下课后见
Okay, class, who would like to give their oral presentation first?
好了 同学们 谁要先报告
Anybody?
谁
Anybody else?
还有谁
Okay, Heather.
好吧 希瑟
- Okay. Can I start?   - Yeah.
- 可以开始了吗  - 可以
Okay, my presentation is on the First Amendment.
我要报告的是第一修正案
And it began on May 25, 1787
这是1787年5月25日
in Philly with George Washington.
华盛顿在费城推动的
And it states, and I quote,
记录上说
"When our Founding Fathers argued
我们的国父争论
the passage of our glorious Constitution..."
我国宪法的变迁
(我知道去年万圣节的事)
(不对 我是指你们杀了人)
The First Amendment gives us the right to say what we want...
第一修正案给我们言论自由
oh, shut the fuck up!
给我闭嘴
So, who's next?
下一个是谁
Uh, Cindy Campbell.
坎 辛蒂
Isn't she the daughter of, well, you know...
她是那个 谁的女儿吗
- Oh, yeah, you know, old Mrs., uh...   - Old Mrs...
- 对 就是她 性感的  - 性感的
Yeah. Yeah, the one and only...
对唯一的
The one and only.
独一无二的
Why, hello, Cindy.
你好 辛蒂
Hi, Principal Squiggman.
校长好
Thanks, Doofy.
谢了 阿呆
It's Special officer Doofy today, Cind.
我今天是特别警探阿呆
Now, Cindy, Sheriffhas some questions
警长有些问题
that he would like to ask you today.
想问你
What is that... god-awful smell?
什么鬼味道
I don't know.
不知道
I got a poopie.
我大便了
Did you just say that you went poopie?
你是说 你拉在裤子上了
Yeah. It was good.
是啊 感觉很棒
- Get him out of here.   - Yes.
- 叫他出去  - 好
- Thank you, Doofy.   - okay.
- 谢谢你阿呆  - 好
You should now go back to Special Ed.
你该回特殊教育班上课了
Okay. Salute.
好 敬礼
Maybe a change of underwear, son.
顺便换条内裤吧
- Bye, Doofy.   - Bye, Cind.
- 拜 阿呆  - 拜 辛蒂
- How are you, Cindy?   - Fine.
- 你好吗 辛蒂  - 很好
How are you, Sheriff?
你呢 警长
Bloated, constipated.
发福又便秘
Got a boil on my ass the size of a walnut. You know, the usual.
屁股上还长了疮 跟以往一样
Cindy, I want to ask you some questions about Drew Decker.
辛蒂 我想问你一些茱儿的事
I didn't really know her.
我跟她不熟
Oh, come on. Sure you do.
拜托 你很熟的
No. I mean, I didn't really know her.
不 我跟她真的不熟
I've been in this game a long time. Don't bullshit a bullshitter.
少来了 别跟我打混
Tell me about Drew.
谈谈茱儿吧
How was she like in bed, Cindy?
她在床上是什么样子
Tried to get you.
只是捉弄你一下
It's an old police trick.
警察就喜欢这样
You didn't fall for it. Good for you, kid.
你不会被骗 很好
Hike! Pass! Pass!
传球 传球
All right, shower up!
好 洗澡了
Yes!
好耶
Yo, Dugan, man, nice play, yo. Word up.
小杜 打的好 够赞!
Johnson, what a block, baby.
强森 阻挡得好
Word up. Woodward. Nice ass.
小伍 好屁股
Damn.
妈的
Yo, Greg, what's up? You gonna hit the showers or what?
格瑞 你要去冲澡吗
No, man. I think I'm gonna work out, beat the bag a little.
不 我要去打沙包 运动一下
Suit yourself, kid. All right.
随你便好吧
Last one in the shower's a rotten egg!
最后冲澡的是大笨蛋
Come on, y'all! I'm gonna get y'all!
快啊 我要痛扁你们啰
Don't let Uncle Ray catch you!
别让雷叔叔逮到你了
(我都知道)
Who did this? Huh? Where are you?
这是谁干的 你在哪
This isn't funny, all right?
这不好玩
A small dick's like a disability, man!
鸡鸡这么小可以算残障了
Would you make fun of a guy in a wheelchair? Huh? Would you?
你怎么可以欺负残障同胞
Come on out here, you sick fuck!
出来 你这个大变态
I'll kick the shit out of you right now! All right?
我要打的你满地找牙
It's not the size of the hammer,
大小不重要
it's the nail you're throwing it at!
重要的是好不好用
It's a shame how she died.
她死了 真可惜
She was such a nice girl.
她是个好女孩
Yeah, she used to baby-sit my brother Doofy.
是啊 她照顾过我弟阿呆
He had the biggest crush on her.
他爱死她了
Ray, you're a dead man.
小雷 你死定了
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
怎么
You wanna get butt-naked and wrestle?
想光着身子摔角
Bring it on, Ray!
来吧
Hold my earrings. Where's my Vaseline?
帮我拿耳环 润滑剂呢
Take it easy. What's the problem?
别激动 怎么回事
I'll show you the problem.
我拿给你看
Oh... That's you?
这是你
They... They turned the hot water off in the showers, all right?
那时候热水没了 我冲冷水
Laugh it up, you guys. Big laugh.
笑吧 笑大声点
You know what? You can all go to hell!
你们都去死吧
Greg, you're not the only one who got one.
不是只有你这样
Oh, you mean Bobby's got a baby dick too?
怎么 巴比也一样小
No. I was talking about the note.
不 我是说收到警告
I got one too.
我也收到了
Somebody knows.
有人知道
That's bullshit, Cindy.
不可能
Someone's just trying to fuck with us.
有人想搞我们
We have to call the police, Greg.
我们得报警
You call the police, and I'll kill you myself.
你报警 我就宰了你
You're hurting her, man.
你伤到她了
And you know what? That goes for all of you guys.
你们最好都注意点
That psycho wants a piece of me, bring it on.
那变态想杀我 那就来吧
But I'm not going to jail. You got that?
我才不要去坐牢 懂吗
What's everybody talking about?
大家在说什么
Just forget it, Shorty. You already know too much.
算了 矮子 你知道太多了
(妙龄小姐选拔)
Aren't they beautiful?
他们漂亮吗
Buffy!
棒透了
Contestant number one!
一号参赛者
Very good. And contestant number two.
很好 二号参赛者
Very good. And contestant number three.
很好 三号参赛者
Buffy! That's my girl!
那是我马子
That's my girlfriend!
Yeah, that's my girlfriend too!
那也是我马子
- Hey, kiss my ass!   - Yeah, I'm hitting that too!
- 去死吧  - 我也跟她搞过
All right, Buffy!
好耶 帕妃
Hey, shut the hell up, man!
闭上你的鸟嘴
The best pussy I ever had!
她可火辣了
What, you want a piece of me?
怎么想打架
Now the talent portion of the competition.
现在进行才艺比赛
Oh, you guys, I'm gonna go downstairs for a closer seat.
我要去楼下看
See you after the show.
待会儿见
Number three, Buffy Gilmore.
三号参赛者 吉帕妃
Hey, you know what? I'm gonna go hit the head.
我要上厕所
You want me to bring you back anything?
想喝什么吗
No, no, no. I'm good, man. But hurry back. She's gonna perform.
不用 快回来 她要表演了
Don't worry. I'll be back.
马上回来
Good evening, Buffy.
晚安 帕妃
And what will be your talent for this evening?
你要表演什么才艺
Acting. I'll be doing a dramatic reading.
演戏 我要演戏
Yeah, yeah! Buffy Gilmore doing a dramatic reading.
吉帕妃要演戏
Hey, do that thing from Baywatch! She's running down the beach!
演海滩游侠的桥段 喇叭小姐
Look out, Greg! Look behind you!
小心背后 格瑞
It's him! It's the killer!
是他 是凶手
Oh, my God! Somebody do something!
天啊 快救命啊
Somebody do something!
快来人救命啊
He's killing him!
他会杀了他
Must be an original piece.
真有创意
He's killing him!
他在追杀他
She's good. She's good.
她不错 她很棒
What's wrong with you people?
你们是怎么回事
That's fantastic.
太好了
You fucking bastards! Why won't anyone help?
你们为何不去救他
- Amazing.   - She's the next Pamela Lee.
- 真棒  - 她是下一个性感巨星
Oh, God! Oh, God! Don't!
天啊 住手
Greg, hold on!
格瑞 撑着点
Give it up for Buffy Gilmore! Beautiful.
请为帕妃鼓掌太棒了
Absolutely fantastic.
太好了
I think we have a winner, ladies and gentlemen.
冠军已经诞生
Miss Buffy Gilmore!
帕妃小姐
Buffy, wait. You have to go back onstage.
帕妃 等等 你得回台上去
No. I have to get to Greg.
不 我得去找格瑞
But you won!
你赢了
They're calling your name.
他们在叫你
There's a killer...
外面有凶手
I won?
赢了
They're calling your name. Go.
他们在叫你 快去
Buffy, what happened? What about Greg?
怎么回事 格瑞呢
Oh, fuck Greg. I won.
管他的我赢了
- Congratulations!   - Oh, out of my way, loser!
- 恭喜  - 滚开 输家
Miss Buffy Gilmore!
帕妃小姐
Give me my crown, bitch.
给我王冠
There's no sign of him anywhere.
到处都找不到他
He could've taken the body.
他可能把尸体弄走了
That's impossible, Cindy.
不可能
There's no blood. There's nothing. Look around.
没血迹 什么都没有
I bet it's just Greg playing...
我想格瑞只是开玩笑
another one of his dumb jokes.
一定找得到他
He's gonna turn up. I'm sure of it.
他肯定会出现的 我确定
He's probably at my house waiting for us right now,you guys.
他也许正在我家等我们呢
All right, fine.
好吧
But you know what? I'm gonna look around some more, so...
但我还要到处找看看
You mind catching a ride home with Buffy?
你跟帕妃回家吧
Yeah, no problem.
好
- All right, fine.   - Call me later.
- 好吧  - 打电话给我
Hello.
喂
Hello, Cindy.
辛蒂
Who is this?
你是谁
It's me, Bobby.
是我 巴比
You know, your boyfriend.
你男友
Yeah, I'm sorry. I guess I'm a little jumpy lately.
抱歉 我想我太紧张了
Hey, any sign of Greg?
找到格瑞了
No.
没有
Do you want me to come by?
你要我过去吗
No.
不用
I'm just gonna take a bath, and then I'm gonna go to bed.
我正在洗澡 之后就要睡了
Okay. I'd really like to see you,
好吧 我真的很想见你
but... I love you.
不过 我爱你
Aw. I love you too, baby.
我也爱你
Bobby, I told you...
巴比 我说过了
I still know what you did last Halloween.
我知道你去年万圣节干的好事
Who is this?
你是谁
Hello.
喂
I'm gonna kill you.
我要杀了你
I'm gonna slice you up.
砍死你
Who is this?
你是谁
I'm gonna chop you like liver.
我会把你剁碎
What do you want?
你想干嘛
I'm in the house.
我就在屋里
Do you know where I am?
知道我在哪吗
I could be anywhere. I'm like the wind, baby.
可能是任何角落 我快如闪电
Yeah. Where am I?
我在哪里
Um, you're-you're behind the couch.
你在沙发后面
What? How do you know that?
什么 你怎么知道
I can, um, see your feet.
我看得到你的脚
Ah! Okay, turn around.
好吧 转身
Close your eyes. No peeking.
闭上眼睛 不准偷看
Yeah. No. No. No.
好耶 不 不对
Hey, no peeking. No peeking. Turn around.
不准偷看 转过去
Good.
很好
Okay, now you look.
好 找找看
Now do you know where I am? You don't.
现在你不知道我在哪里了吧
No, Mr. Killer. I don't know where you are.
杀手先生 我不知道
I'll give you a big clue.
告诉你吧
Oh! I gotta stop drinking.
我该戒酒了
- Grandma!   - Ow, baby!
- 奶奶  - 宝贝
Oh, my hip!
我的腰
(119出了什么事)
White woman in trouble off the 744...
744公路有白人女性出事了
Are you okay?
你还好吧
I heard screaming. What's going on?
我听到尖叫 怎么了
Bobby, he was here.
他刚才在这里
The killer was here, Bobby.
就是凶手 巴比
It's okay.
没事了
I can explain that.
我能解释
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
Afriend gave 'em to me. Cindy. Cindy.
有个朋友给我的
Cindy. Cindy!
辛蒂 辛蒂
Cindy! Cindy! Cindy!
辛蒂
It's me, Cind.
是我 辛蒂
Cindy, you know me. Cindy.
辛蒂 你了解我的
I know you've had a rough night, Cindy,
我知道你很难过
so I won't keep you.
我不耽误你
I just want you to look at some photos.
我想请你看几张照片
Tell me what you think.
告诉我你的看法
No?
不
No.
I'm sorry, Sheriff.
抱歉 警长
You sure?
你确定
Okay, you're free to go.
好吧 你可以走了
Do you have somebody picking you up?
有人送你吗
- Yeah.   - Oh. Just...
- 好吧  - 再
Just check that one out again.
再看一张吧
Mm, no.
不行
No? No? Well, worth a shot. All right, thanks.
好吧 不喜欢就算了
Guess what I just did with those hookers we busted.
你猜我跟逮到的妓女做了什么
No way.
不会吧
All the way, man! Yes, yes. Watch this.
没错 你看着
- Doofy!   - Yeah?
- 阿呆  - 埃
- Come on. Come on.   - Okay.
- 过来  - 好
Special officer Doofy reporting.
特别警探阿呆报到
Hey, Doofy, smell my fingers.
阿呆 闻闻我的手指
What's that?
那是什么
That's when you know you've become a man, Doofy!
等你成了男人就知道了
Hey, Terry, smell my finger.
泰瑞 闻闻我的手指
- What the hell is that?   - My ass.
- 那是什么鬼味道  - 我的屁眼
Get the hell out of here, Doofy.
快滚吧
Doofy. Mom said get home now.
阿呆 妈说现在回家
Tell Mom I'm on official police business.
告诉妈 我在忙着扮警察
Cindy, are you okay?
辛蒂 你还好吧
Hey, hey, hey. No talking to the witness.
不准跟证人交谈
Go get in the car, Doofy. She's coming with us.
去开车 她跟我们走
Does Mom know?
妈知道吗
Yeah, Doofus.
知道
Mom says when I wear this badge,
妈说我戴徽章
you're supposed to treat me like a man of the law.
你就得尊敬我
Mom also said for you to stop sticking your dick in the vacuum cleaner.
妈也叫你别用吸尘器吸小弟弟
(警察局2017年成立)
Okay, three, two...
好 三 二
Oh, no. Gosh darn.
不 该死
What now?
又怎么了
It's just that there's all these numbers with deci...
这些数字
What, can't you count?
怎么你不会算术
No, I can count, but there's really...
那简单
Let me make it easy for you. Listen up, okay?
肥猪仔细听我说
This little piggy went to the market.
这只小猪去了市场
This little piggy stayed home.
这只小猪留在家里
Now, if this little piggy doesn't roll the goddamn camera...
要是这只猪不拍摄
I'm gonna put my foot up his fuckin' ass...
我就踢他屁股
We're live, Gail.
现场播出了
Gail Hailstorm standing out front of the police station...
海盖儿在警局外
where I'm going to try and get a glimpse of Cindy Campbell,
我们正设法找到坎辛蒂
the young girl who was attacked earlier this evening.
她今晚稍早遭受攻击
- You're on my foot, fat shit!   - Sorry, G...
- 你踩到我了 猪头  - 对不起
What did I say?
我是怎么说的
"Don't ever step on Gail's shoes."
别踩到盖儿的鞋
Why not?
为什么
Because Gail wears Prada shoes.
因为盖儿穿名牌鞋
You idiot.
你这个猪头
I'm a bad man.
我很皮的
Cindy, can we get a statement?
辛蒂 请说句话吧
Buffy Gilmore, Miss Teen.
我是妙龄小姐
She's not talking.
她不想说
Is it true the police have someone in custody?
警方有扣留任何人吗
Come on, Cindy.
走吧 辛蒂
Cindy, Cindy, your ass looks fat!
你屁股真肥
Bitch!
贱人
Good shot.
打的好
Come on.
走吧
All right, who copped a feel?
谁摸我
Gail, it was me.
是我
- Oh, my God.   - It was an accident, Gail.
- 我的天啊  - 这是意外
I only touched it, the top of the breast.
我只是摸了乳尖
It was so tender and juicy.
真是柔软
Shut up!
闭嘴
- Yo.   - Hello, Shorty. What are you doing?
- 喂  - 矮子 你在干嘛
Nothin'. Sittin' here watchin' the game. Smokin' some bud.
没什么 我在看比赛 哈些草
Are you all alone?
你一个人吗
Wassup?
大家好
What the... Who's that?
搞什么 那是谁
Yo, pick up the phone.
听电话
Wassup?
你好
Yo, Dookie, pick up the phone!
小杜 听电话
- Yo.   - Wassup?
- 喂  - 干嘛
- What you doin', son?   - Nothin'. Just chillin', killin'.
- 你呢  - 没什么 到处砍人啰
True. True.
很好 很好
So you think Bobby did it?
是巴比吗
I don't know. But he was there, Buffy.
不知道 但他在场
I knew there had to be something. He's just too perfect.
我就知道他有问题 他太完美了
Handsome, smart, good in bed.
英俊 聪明 又很能"干"
What did you say?
你说什么
Hey, Cind. Got your ice pack for your hand.
辛蒂 冰敷袋来了
Sorry.
抱歉
I'll get you one for your head.
我再拿一个来敷头
No, no, that's okay, Doofy.
不用了 阿呆
Hey, we're gonna get that guy you dumped in the water. Yeah.
我们去逮你们丢进水里的人吧
I'll be next door if you need me.
我就在隔壁
Night, Cind.
晚安 辛蒂
Buffy, you told him?
你告诉他了
The moron overheard a conversation Greg and I were having.
那白痴听见我跟格瑞交谈
Yeah, but what if he says something?
万一他说出去怎么办
Who's gonna believe a retarded retard like him anyway?
谁会相信他
Don't worry.
别担心
Cindy, telephone.
辛蒂 电话
Thank you.
谢谢
Hello.
喂
Hello, Cindy.
辛蒂 你好
Guess what.
你猜怎么着
No!
不
You got the wrong guy.
你们逮错人了
No!
不是
- Doofy!   - Yep, It's not Bobby.
- 阿呆  - 不是巴比
Who is this?
你是谁
Hello?
喂
I said don't disturb me while I'm cleaning my room!
说过我清理房间时别来烦我的
I heard Bobby got out this morning.
听说巴比今早获释了
I haven't seen him around. Is he pissed?
我没看到他 他生气吗
You mean since you branded him the Candyman?
你是说你诬指他是凶手
No. His heart is broken.
不 他伤心死了
Yo, son. It's like I seen this all before.
这场景有点似曾相识呢
They had a killer at your old high school, Shorty?
你以前的学校有杀手
No, it was in this movie Scream.
不很"惊声尖叫"
Same dialogue and everything. This is ill.
真糟糕
- How did it end?   - I don't know.
- 结局怎样  - 不知道
Some niggas started shooting up in the movie theater,
有黑鬼在电影院里火拼
so we just broke out.
我们就跑出来了
No doubt.
没错
Okay, I say we all just stick together.
好吧 今晚到我家集合
Tonight everyone meet at my house.
And bring some friends. But don't tell everyone.
带些朋友来 别四处张扬
Try to keep it quiet.
口风紧一点
Okay.
好
Yo! Party at Cindy's house! Drunk white women for everybody!
辛蒂家开派对 大家有得乱搞了
Ray, if you see Bobby, tell him I love him.
要是看到巴比跟他说我爱他
Okay. If I see Bobby, I'll tell him I love him.
好 如果我看到他 我会说我爱他
Jesus!
天啊
It's okay. It's all right. It's just me, baby.
没关系 是我 宝贝
- What, you don't still think it's me, do you?   - No.
- 你还认为是我  - 不
It's just that somebody did try to kill me.
但的确有人想杀我
And the police said I scared him away.
警方说我吓跑他了
I know. He called me last night.
我知道 他昨晚打电话给我
You see, it couldn't have been me. I was in jail last night. Remember?
看吧 不可能是我 我被关着
You're the best.
你真行
I'm sorry. Please understand.
抱歉 请你体谅
Understand what? That my girlfriend would rather
体谅你把我
call me a killer than touch me?
当成凶手
That's not true, Bobby.
不是的
Then what is it?
那你是怎么了
What is it? She's gone and she's not coming back.
她走了 她不会再回来了
It's been over a year, Cindy.
已经一年多了 辛蒂
But Ginger was such an important part of the Spice Girls.
但辣妹合唱团不能没有她
Oh, you gotta move on, baby.
日子还是要过的
I'm sorry if my complicated life...
抱歉 我的生活太复杂了
is an inconvenience to your perfect existence.
这对你实在不公平
Cindy. Cind.
辛蒂 辛蒂
Okay, everybody, listen up.
大家听清楚了
Let me just say, uh,
我这么说吧
the killing of these teenagers has been tragic, but, uh...
这些青少年被杀实在是悲剧
Hey, you know, shit happens.
坏事总是年年有
Sheriff! Sheriff!
警长 警长
Yes, Miss Thunderstorm.
是的 找碴小姐
Have they found Cindy Campbell's father?
找到辛蒂的父亲了吗
No.
不
Isn't he a suspect?
他不是嫌犯
That is classified information. Where are you getting that?
这是机密 你怎么知道
I'm sorry, but my sources are strictly confidential, Sheriff.
抱歉 我不能透露资讯来源
Hey, Gail.
嗨 盖儿
Gail swallows.
盖儿爱吃小弟弟
Watch this.
看着
Hello. Who is this?
是谁
What?
什么
You wanna kill me?
你想杀我
Oh, God. Hold on.
等等
Cindy, it's for you.
辛蒂 找你的
All right, knock it off, Buffy.
别捉弄辛蒂了 帕妃
Now, as you all have heard, there is a killer in town...
你们都听说过 镇上有凶手
and the police have asked us to give you the following safety tips.
警方给了我们一些安全准则
Stay in well-lit areas.
待在灯光明亮的地方
Do not travel alone whenever possible.
不要单独旅行
Always wipe front to back.
卫生纸由前往后擦
And remember, never, ever believe someone...
记住 千万不要相信别人
when they tell you that shaving your pubic hair...
尤其是想帮你
will rid you of crab infestation.
刮毛的人
Now, I understand this is a difficult time for you young ladies.
我知道你们很难过
So if anyone needs to come to my office to talk,
如果有人想找我谈
I am here for you.
到办公室找我
What a crock of shit.
一堆屁话
It's not, Buffy!
才不是呢
He's real!
他是当真的
Miss Mann?
木兰老师
Come in, dear. Have a seat. Take off your bra if you'd like.
请进 请坐 把胸罩脱了吧
No, thanks.
不 谢了
What can I do for you, Cindy?
需要我帮忙吗
I need to talk. See, I have this problem...
我需要谈谈 我有个问题
and I don't know who to tell.
我不知该跟谁说
Not feeling so fresh?
感觉很不清爽
Feminine odor and itching got you down?
阴道发痒
Uh, no. No, not that.
不 不是的
Then what is it?
那是什么
I have a terrible secret.
我有个恐怖的秘密
Well, Cindy, we all have our little secrets.
人都有秘密的
Sometimes we do things we're not so proud of.
有时我们会做些不光彩的事
Some for money,
有些人为钱
others to gain the athletic edge on the competition.
有些人是为了测试自己的极限
Sometimes those secrets come back to haunt us.
这些秘密有时会反噬我们
Do you know what I mean?
知道我的意思吗
Yes, I do, um, Miss Mann. Thanks for ball...
我知道 谢谢蛋蛋
I mean, all your help. I have to go to class.
我是指 你的协助 我得去上课了
Anytime, dear.
随时欢迎你
Buffy, are you coming?
帕妃 要来吗
I'll catch up with you guys in a sec.
我马上到
Redrum.
死神到了
Hello?
你好
Somebody there?
有人吗
Hello!
你好
Very funny.
真可笑
Who put you up to this, Cindy?
谁叫你打扮成这样 辛蒂
Lose the cape. It's way too '90s horror.
披风脱掉 太老套了
Oh, so what movie is this from, Die, Cheerleader, Die?
这是哪部电影的情节 啦啦队长之死
Wanna play psycho killer?
想演变态凶手
Can I be the helpless cheerleader?
那我演无助的啦啦队长吧
Oh, so this is where I'm supposed to beg for my life?
那我该求你放过我啰
Please, Mr. Killer, don't kill me.
求求你 凶手先生 别杀我
So is this where I'm supposed to bleed?
我该在这里流血
Oh, look, I'm bleeding!
看 我流血了
Oh, yeah, I'm supposed to run, right?
我该逃了 对吧
Okay. I'm running! I'm running! Help!
我在逃 我在逃了 救命
Help! Now I'm gonna fall and break my leg, leaving me helpless.
现在我该跌断腿 孤立无援
There you go, Mr. Scary Killer. I'm panicking now.
好了 凶手先生 我很慌了
Oh, God! Somebody please help me!
天啊 快来人救救我
Oh, God, no!
天啊 不
Oh, now what?
现在呢
I guess this is the big climax.
我想这是全片高潮了
Hope you don't mind if I fake it. Aah!
希望你不会觉得我演太假了
Oh, look at me. I'm all dead.
看看我 我死了
I'm a gross, scary severed head. Come on. Please.
我是颗恶心的头颅 拜托
Do you know who I am? I'm Miss Teen.
知道是谁吗 我是妙龄小姐
You're really giving me a headache.
你让我的头好痛
And you got blood all over my Gucci sweater.
你把我的古奇T恤染上血了
I hope you're gonna pay for that.
希望你会付出代价
(失物招领)
Ah! I will not be ignored by the likes...
啊 我不会被忽略
I'm gonna jump!
我要跳了
Phil, get back in there.
菲尔 回来
- No!   - What are you doing up there?
- 不  - 你在上面干嘛
Be reasonable.
理智点
I can't take this fucking job or those greasy shithead teenagers anymore!
我不要再教这些白烂学生了
I'm going to end it all!
我要结束这一切
Wait! Hold on! We're getting help for you!
等等 我们正在找人帮忙
Now we know Bobby's not the killer. So who is?
凶手不是巴比 那是谁
I don't know.
不知道
If the killer was in your house last night,
昨晚凶手在你家
why didn't he just kill you then?
为何不杀你
Because he's just messing with us.
他只想耍我们
Don't you see? He's got us right where he wants us.
而他也的确达到目的了
We can't go to the police.
我们不能找警察
He's just out there watching us and waiting for us.
他正在等着我们
What are you waiting for, huh?
你还在等什么
What are you waiting for?
你还等什么
What am I waiting for?
我还等什么
What are you waiting for?
你还等什么
Fuck you!
去你妈的
Oh, my God.
我的老天
Ray, I still don't think this party is a good idea.
我还是不认为开派对是好主意
You know I'm not gonna let nothin' happen to you.
我会保护你的
I just don't feel right.
我只是觉得有危险
Why can't we just do something else?
我们为何不能做点别的
How about we go to the movies?
去看电影吧
Huh? You like that? See a little movie, huh?
你喜欢看电影
Hey! This is my song!
我最喜欢这首歌
You know they gave me a shout-out on the album, right?
我还有机会在里面叫几声呢
What?
什么
ooh, Brenda.
没错
Everywhere I go I see the same ho's
不管走到哪 我都看到那贱人
Did I tell you how sexy you look in my jersey?
你穿我的运动衣很性感
I do, Ray?
真的
Yes.
没错
I like it. Hey, get up. Go over there. Let me see it.
我喜欢 过来点 让我看看
Ooh! Yes, I like that.
继续 好耶 我喜欢
- You like that? You like that?   - Yeah. Hey!
- 你喜欢 你喜欢  - 是
Hey, put this on with it.
把这穿上
Ray, you are so freaky.
小雷 你真怪
That's right. You know I'm freaky, girl.
没错 我是大变态
Go on. Pull it. Pull it up.
继续 穿好
Yeah. Here. Put this on with it.
来 把这戴上
Go on.
快啊
Are you sure?
你确定
Go on, girl. Go on. Pull it on.
快啊 戴上 快啊
- Okay.   - Go on.
- 好的  - 继续
I like that look.
我喜欢
Ooh! I'm bad.
我很坏的
Here. Put this on with it.
是啊 来 把这戴上
Go on, girl. Put it on.
快啊 戴上它
Yeah. Put that shit on there. Come on. Just shove it on.
快 把那玩意戴上 用力戴
Do it. Yeah. Ooh, so fucking sexy.
好耶 真性感
Come here, girl. Bring your little sexy ass over here. Come on!
过来 性感的小屁屁
Full speed. Charge!
用力给我抱抱
Yes! Yes! Come on! Turn around!
快啊 转过来
Turn around! Come on!
转过来
Yes, Brendan! Take it, Brendan! Take it, Brendan!
好耶 接招吧 布兰蛋
Who?
谁
Uh... Uh, Brenda. Put the helmet on.
布兰妲 快 把安全帽戴上
No, let's role-play. Come on. You get me.
不 来玩角色扮演
Come on! Come on!
快 换你来上我
I'm here at Lover's Lookout.
我正在幽会停车场
It's dark, it's in the middle of nowhere,
这里很黑 很偏僻
and it's where hormone-driven teens love to come and fool around.
那些青少年就爱来这里爽
So very likely we're about to see someone get killed.
我们应该能看到有人被杀
Okay, sure enough, there's a girl in that car,
那车里有个女孩
blouse unbuttoned, all alone.
上衣松开
Let's see if she'll have a word with us.
看看她有没有话要说
Hi. Gail Hailstorm, author of the new book You're Next.
嗨 我是盖儿 新书《下一个就是你》的作者
Can you tell us your name?
你叫什么名字
Well, my name's Heather.
希瑟
Can you tell us what you're doing out here all alone?
告诉我们你为何一个人在此
Well, yeah, sure.
好 没问题
My boyfriend and I were just, like, making out...
我男友和我来这里玩耍
and then we heard a noise out there, so he went to go check it,
接着我们听到声音 他去查探
but... well, that was, like, ten minutes ago.
那是十分钟前的事了
Yeah, yeah. Has it crossed your little mind that
你想他
your boyfriend was probably murdered...
是不是遇害了
and you're about to be slaughtered next?
而你就是下一个
- Really? No way!   - Way.
- 真的 不可能  - 可能
Heather, good luck.
好祝好运
Okay, thanks, Gail. You're the best.
谢了 你真优秀
Just as I thought. The murder is happening as we speak.
我知道 正如我所想 凶手已经出现
I'm going to try and break into the bloodshed.
我会设法拍下凶案过程
Are you getting this?
准备
Excuse me. Heather, can you tell us what you're feeling, honey?
抱歉 请问你现在感觉如何
Lots of pain. Gail, please help me.
很痛 救救我
Gail, please!
救救我
I'd like to help you out, kid, but it's sweeps.
我很想救你 但要先拼收视率
Sir, sir, can I get a word with you?
先生 你有话要说吗
You got a lot of nerve coming here.
敢来这里算你勇敢
I'm just trying to do my job.
我只是扮演好我的角色
Get the camera off me now! You're dead, bitch.
移开摄影机
No, Kenny, keep rolling!
继续拍
I'm gonna slice your head off and shove it up his ass.
你死定了 我要跺下你的头
Get that camera off me!
移开摄影机
Oh, my God, Kenny!
天啊 肯尼
Kenny, move your fat ass!
肯尼 把你的肥屁股移开点
Kenny! Oh, my God, he's right behind you!
天啊他就在身后
This man is chasin'Miss Gail.
这人正在追盖儿
I'm so scared right now.
我好害怕
I just want to say... to the family of my cameraman, Kenny,
我只想 对摄影师肯尼的家人说
I am so sorry.
我很抱歉
This was my interview,
这是我的采访
my story.
我的报导
It's all my fault.
一切都是我的错
(莎翁情史)
You want some popcorn?
来点爆米花
Uh-uh. I brought me a little snack of my own.
我自己带了点零食来
- You want some chicken?   - Nah.
- 想吃炸鸡吗  - 不
(请安静观赏)
Mm-hmm. For all y'all talkers up in here,
爱讲话的
it's time to keep it down right now.
现在该闭上鸟嘴了
Shh, back at you. Shh!
后面的安静点
Why they actin' already?
干嘛
It ain't nothin' but the previews.
现在还在放预告片啊
(预告限不成熟的观众看)
The largest ship the world had ever known.
世上最大的一艘船
Its 400 passengers and crew on a maiden voyage to a brave new world.
四百名乘客和船员 首航出发前往新世界
Ajourney that would change their lives forever.
一趟永远改变他们命运的旅程
I'm the king of the world!
我是世界之王
(史蒂芬·阿匹柏 最新钜作 《勇者无惧2》)
Get your ass back down there, boy!
快给我下来
I'm gonna go to the bathroom real quick.
我要去上厕所
The movie about to come on.
电影要开演了
- I gotta go to the bathroom.   - Here. Take your hot sauce.
- 我得上厕所  - 拿好你的辣酱
Hurry up, man. Don't be long.
快点 别太久了 不会很久的
Back up! Let him through!
让开 让他过去
You can move back some. You don't own the theater.
往后坐一点 戏院又不是你的
(保证你当爸爸)
And they're off!
开始了
It's number three in the lead. Number two close behind.
二号紧跟在后 三号赢了
And number three is the winner!
二号紧接在后
Number two has placed, and number four to show.
四号第三
Next week's Triple Crown starts at 2:30.
下周比赛二点半开始
Be here early.
要早点到
Hey, who was that?
是谁啊
Go ahead. Do it again. Do it again.
继续 再来一次
Mm-mmm! Don't go in there!
我的天 别进去
Lord, I'm gonna have a heart attack!
我快休克了
Man, this is some scary shit!
这真是吓人
Oh, I am scared!
我好害怕
Excuse me.
抱歉
I think I paid my money like everybody else up in here.
我跟大家一样付钱进来的
That ain't no man.
她不是男的
You can see her real hair right there!
看的到她的真发呢
Do you mind?
拜托你
I know you better get outta my face!
你最好别来惹我
Outta my face! Outta my face!
别惹我 滚开
This is all me up in here. You handle that.
我有权说话 接受吧
Will you shut the fuck up!
你闭嘴好吗
Mmm, mmm. This movie is good.
这部片子真好看
Hey, baby. You came back just in time.
宝贝 你回来的正是时候
She's about to get it on with Shakespeare.
布莱德彼特的前女友真怪
- She dressing like a man...   - Shut up.
- 她扮成男  - 闭嘴
Yeah, I got you. I got you on camera.
我逮到你了 我录下你了
You on Candid Camera now.
你被我录影存证了
You ain't know that.
没想到吧
Hello. Hey, girl. Uh-uh. I'm in the movie.
喂 我在看电影呢
Shakespeare In Love.
莎翁情史
Uh-uh. Ooh! You lying.
乱讲
For Christ's sake, will you just shut your trap!
天啊 闭上你的鸟嘴吧
- Shut up!   - Hold on.
- 闭嘴  - 等等
I don't know why y'all is actin'like this.
你们干嘛这样
My girlfriend already seen the movie.
我朋友看过
She said they don't even stay together in the end.
她说结局很烂
Give me that. Right on.
给我那个 好耶
Will you sit down.
坐下好吗
Shut up.
闭嘴
Your ass is grass.
臭婆娘
- This is for Thelma   - And Louise!
- 我为女主角报仇  - 还有男主角
This is for talking through The Fugitive!
谁叫你拼命讲话
- You ruined Schindler's List.   - Jackie Chan movies.
- 你毁了辛德勒的名单  - 成龙的电影
Boogie Nights!
不羁夜
And Big Momma's House!
还有超级奶霸
And I cannot marry the daughter of Sir Robert De Lesseps.
我不能娶罗拔的女儿
Um, you guys, there's a few too many people.
各位 人数太多了
Oh, honey, please don't throw... Hey, you guys, stop.
拜托 别吐 住手
Hey! Hey, please! That's my dad's!
那是我爸的
- No, don't touch... Ah, no!   - Do you have more beer?
- 别碰  - 你还有啤酒吗
Do you have more beer?
你还有啤酒吗
Um, yeah. Uh, check in the garage.
有 去车库找一找
No, no, no, no! Don't!
不 不
(杀手撒旦牌)
Kitty, you scared me.
猫咪 你吓到我了
Horsey. Oh, you scared me too.
马儿 你也吓到我了
Hello? Who's there?
是谁
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Please, don't!
天啊 不要
Please! I'm just a day player!
拜托 我只是临时演员
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
喝 喝 喝
Oh, Bobby. Bobby. I was worried about you.
巴比 我好担心你
I thought the killer got to you before I could.
我以为凶手先找到你了
Could what?
会吗
I wanna go upstairs. There's something I wanna show you.
我想上楼 我想让你看点东西
Hey, party on!
继续玩吧
- So...   - So.
- 怎样  - 怎样
Here we are... again.
我们又在一起了
And, you know, if you're not ready,
你知道 如果你还没准备好
I'll understand.
我能了解
Bobby. I am ready.
我准备好了
- You are?   - Yeah.
- 真的  - 对
I can't keep fighting these urges.
我无法抵抗我的欲望
I have to just give in to them...
我想放开一切
and let them flow.
纵情享受
Right.
巴比
Bobby?
什么
I have been so selfish.
我一直都太自私了
This is like a scene from a movie or something.
这好像某部电影的片段
Only it isn't a movie, Bobby.
但这不是电影 巴比
This is real life.
这是真的
It's all a movie, baby.
这是部电影
There's the sound guy. There's the script supervisor.
收音师在那 工作人员都在
How ya doin', baby?
你们好吗
- Bobby?   - What?
- 巴比  - 干嘛
What I mean is that in real life...
我指的是 在真实生活中
you have to enjoy each moment.
你得享受一切
Bobby. Bobby!
巴比 巴比
Can I tell you a secret?
我能跟你讲个秘密吗
Sure, man.
说吧
I see dead people.
我看得见鬼魂
Man, this shit is awesome!
哇 这玩意炫呆了
Yo, son, we gotta roll some more of that shit!
你该多卷一点来抽
We don't have any more papers, man.
但我们没烟纸了
We don't have any more papers.
我们没烟纸了
Oh, man! What can we use to make a bong?
我们可以用水管干嘛
Toke! Toke! Toke! Toke! Toke! Toke! Toke!
吸 吸 吸
Toke! Toke! Toke! Toke! Toke! Toke! Toke! Toke!
Oh, shit, son!
妈的
This some good shit!
这玩意酷毙了
- Bobby! I've never done this before.   - What?
- 巴比 我没有做过  - 什么
It's okay. It's okay.
没关系
It's just like... It's like sucking on a Tootsie Roll Pop.
那就像 那就像在吃棒棒糖
- ATootsie Pop?   - Yeah, a cherry-flavor one.
- 棒棒糖  - 对 樱桃口味的
With the fudge in the middle?
中间有软糖的那种
Okay.
好耶
Just like that.
就是这样
Just like that, baby.
Oh! Jesus!
天啊
I never could wait to get to the chewy middle.
我每次都等不及就用咬的
- You know, let me.   - Oh.Okay.
- 让我来吧  - 好的
Goddamn!
哇咧
Guess it's been a while.
已经很久了
It's very, uh, '70s of you.
你的毛真劲爆
Oh, Bobby!
快 巴比
Come here, Bobby! I want it now!
巴比 我要
Oh, man, am I fuckin' stoned!
天啊 我爽呆了
Yeah, me too, son.
我也是
Hey, you guys hear that?
你们听见了吗
Hello?
你好
- Hello?   - Hello?
- 你好  - 你好
What's your favorite scary movie?
你最喜欢哪部恐怖片
Let me talk to her. Shh!
让我跟她说话
I'm gonna gut you like a pig!
我要把你的内脏都挖出来
Oh, yeah!
真爽
What's my name, Bobby?
我是谁 巴比
What?
什么
What's my name, bitch?
我是谁
Ow! God!
天哪
It's Cindy!
是辛蒂
Whose is it, Bobby?
谁最行 巴比
It's yours.
是你
Oh, my God!
我的天啊
Oh, shit!
妈的
Yo! That was the illest rhyme I ever seen, son!
这是我听过最棒的了
Bobby...
巴比
where were you tonight?
你今晚本来在哪里
What?
什么
I was just curious.
我只是好奇
What took you so long to get here?
你怎么拖这么久才来
Why you so curious?
你怎么这么好奇
I don't know.
我不知道
I thought it would fit the '90s horror cliche...
我以为会跟烂恐怖片一样
if you turned out to be the killer.
结果你才是凶手
Oh, so, what? You thinkI killed Buffy and Greg?
你认为是我杀了帕妃和格瑞
Buffy and Greg are dead?
帕妃和格瑞死了
I thought you knew that.
我以为你知道
Oh, my God! Bobby, turn around!
天啊 巴比 转过身去
It's the killer!
是凶手
Cindy!
辛蒂
Oh, my God!
天啊
Bobby! Bobby!
巴比 巴比
Cindy. Help me.
救救我
Bobby, it's okay.
宝贝 没事了
Gimme the gun.
把枪给我
It's gonna be okay, Bobby.
宝贝 你不会有事的
Yo, wait for me!
等等我
There's a killer in the house!
凶手在这里
There's ass, blood and guts everywhere!
到处都是血
Someone done gone crazy, son!
有人发疯了
We all go a little crazy sometimes.
我们多少都会发疯的
Bobby, no!
巴比 不
Oh, shit, son!
妈的
Oh, my God!
我的天
Cindy, he shot me in the lungs.
他射中我胸口
You wanna hit this shit?
想吸一口吗
Ketchup.
蕃茄酱
Just like my mom puts on her spaghetti, baby.
我妈做意大利面就只放这个
Oh, my God! Ray, you've gotta help me!
天啊 小雷 你得帮我
Bobby's gone crazy!
巴比疯了
Surprise!
惊喜
Surprise, Cindy!
惊喜 辛蒂
Why are you doing this, Bobby?
你为何这么做
Why? Why?
为什么 为什么
You hear that, Ray?
听见吗 小雷
I think she wants a motive.
她要动机
Did Scream have a plot?
"惊声尖叫"有什么剧情
No.
没有
Did I Know What You Did Last Summer make any sense?
"是谁搞的鬼"也烂毙了
Don't think so!
我不这么想
What about the sequel?
续集里
What was with that fat, whiteJamaican kid?
干嘛多了个牙买加白痴
I wanna kill that motherfucker.
我想杀了他 我也是
It was bad casting, Bobby.
演员太烂了
How about this for a motive? Lack of sex!
我觉得根本没激情场面
It can cause serious deviant behavior.
那会导致变态行为
I thought you loved me.
我以为你爱我
Oh, I did, baby. I did.
我爱的 我爱的
But abstinence can make you discover new things about yourself.
但禁欲后能让你重新发掘自己
That's right, Cindy. I'm gay.
辛蒂 我是同志
And in case you haven't noticed,
万一你没注意
so is Ray.
小雷也是
What? I ain't gay.
什么 我才不是
What are you talking about? You took me to that club.
那你为何带我到俱乐部去
So, they play good music.
那又怎样 那里音乐好听啊
What about our trip to San Francisco, then?
去旧金山的事呢
I wanted to go shopping.
我想去购物
- But you made love to me.   - No. First of all, you sucked my...
- 但你跟我做爱了  - 不 是你舔我弟弟
Whatever, Ray! I don't want to talk about this now.
我不想谈了
The point is, I'm a new man,
我要丢下一切
and I'm ready to leave all this behind and start a new life.
开始新生
So you killed all your friends?
你要杀了你所有的朋友
Oh, no.
没有
Just you. And maybe Shorty,
只有你 还有矮子
but that wasn't planned or anything.
但那不是预谋
But here's the genius part.
最天才的部份是
We're copycatting a serial killer that already exists.
我们模仿真正的杀人凶手
It's the perfect crime, Cindy.
这是完全犯罪
But wait! There's more!
等等 还有
Hang on to your seat, baby,
坐稳了
cause this one's a screamer!
这可有趣了
I'll be back.
我马上回来
Move your big ass.Come on.
你快去
Dad!
爸
What are you gonna do, frame him?
你想干嘛 诬陷他
Nah. We're just havin' a little bit of fun with old daddio.
不 我们要玩玩你老爸
The police are gonna find you and daddy both dead,
警方会发现你跟你爸都死了
and me and Ray are the only survivors of a maniac's revenge.
我和小雷是唯一的生还者
You ready?
准备好了吗
- You ready?   - I'm ready.
- 准备好了吗  - 好了
I'm ready to do this shit.
我好了 动手吧
- Come on.   - All right.
- 来吧  - 好的
- 快点  - 好的
- Come on!   - Give it to me.
- 快刺我  - 把刀给我
No! Wait, wait, wait, wait.
等等 等等
- All right. Ready? Let's do this.   - Wait, wait. Ready.
- 准备好了吗 来吧  - 等等
- Come on. Come on.   - Ready.
- 来吧 来吧 快快刺我  - 好了
Give it to me!
动手吧
No! Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
等等
- Remember what we talked about? To the side.   - I know.
- 我们说好的  - 我知道
- How many times we gonna go over this?   - Okay.
- 你要提几次  - 知道了
Stop. Just... All right. Trust me, okay?
我知道的 相信我
- All right. I'm ready.   - Trust me. I got this shit. Ready?
- 准备好了  - 相信我 我知道我在干嘛
- Ready?   - Come on!
- 准备好了吗  - 来吧
Wait, wait, wait!
等等 等等
I'm about to cut your throat, boy!
我要割穿你喉咙了
Stop acting like a little girl. Come on. Come on!
别装了 快点
You're right, you're right, you're right.
你说的对
Yeah, come on!
好了 我好了 来吧
No! You guys are psychos!
你们真变态
You've seen one too many TV shows!
你们看太多电视了
No! Watching television shows doesn't create psycho killers!
不 看电视节目不会造就变态杀手
Cancelin' TV shows does!
取消电视节目才会
The Wayans Brothers was a good show, man!
吴宗宪的节目就超炫
It was a good-ass show,
我们连最后一集
and we didn't even get a final episode!
都没得录
Take it easy! I'm feelin' a little woozy here!
别刺我了 我有点想吐了
It's my turn. Give me the knife.
该我了 把刀给我
Fuck outta here. Ain't nobody stabbin' me.
想都别想 没人能拿刀砍我
Surprise, Cindy!
惊喜 辛蒂
All right, all right.
很好 等等
Hold on a second.
我休息一下
Just give me a moment. Ah. One...
一下就好
Oh, yeah. That's it. Ah. Okay.
好了
Dad!
爸
Are you okay?
你还好吧
I thought I told you not to have a party unless I was here.
我说过我在家才能开派对的
But, Dad, you were here. You were in the closet.
你在啊 你在衣柜里
Oh, yeah, that's right.
没错
Did you get some girlfriends' numbers for me?
帮我要到女生电话了
Dad, they're dead.
她们都死了
Ah, you know, I can't get a break.
我老是不走运
What's that? Is that the cops?
那是什么 警察吗
Okay, okay, listen, honey. Help me up now.
听着 扶我起来
Uh... Uh... If the cops come, tell 'em I'm a plumber, okay?
告诉警察我是水电工
You had a leaky faucet, and you called, and they sent me over.
你的水龙头坏了我来修
We don't know each other.
我们根本不认识
No, no!
不
Dad, Dad, put your arms down.
爸把手放下
What the hell's goin' on here?
怎么回事
Sheriff, it's a bloodbath in there.
里面一片血海
He was right here! I swear it!
他本来在这里我发誓
Who was?
谁
The killer! The guy that murdered all my friends!
凶手 那家伙杀光了我朋友
And the sick bastard planted drugs all in the house there.
那混蛋还在屋里藏毒品
All over the place.
到处都是
Dad. Stop it.
爸 别说了
All right, Cindy. I'm gonna have to take you down to the station.
我得带你回警局
I'm cool, though, right? I'm okay?
我没事吧 我没事吧
Let's... Let's go, Cindy.
走吧 辛蒂
Cindy. Call me.
打电话给我
Daddy'll get you out, honey.
老爸会保你出来的
Let's go over this again.
再重头来过吧
You say it was an accident.
你说那是意外
Yes.
对
He was on the road.
他在路上
And you think he came back to get revenge?
你想他是回来报
It has to be him, Sheriff.
一定是他警长
Here, Sheriff. They wanted me to give this to you.
警长他们要我把这交给你
- That'll be all, Doofy.   - Okay.
- 好了 阿呆  - 好的
- I'm gonna go, then. All right.   - All right.
- 我要走了  - 好
Bye, Cind.
拜 辛蒂
I'm sorry, Cindy. It wasn't the man you guys killed.
抱歉辛蒂不是那个人
His name was David Keegan.
他叫奇大卫
Some fishermen found his body a few weeks later.
一个渔夫发现他的尸体了
He's buried in Lakewood Cemetery.
他被埋在湖林墓园
That's impossible.
不可能
Then I don't know who it could be.
那我真的不知是谁了
He's gotta be someone... who was connected with all the victims,
一定是个知道
someone who knew about the accident.
所有事件的人
Someone who could move around without being noticed.
一个不被人注意的人
Oh, my God.
我的天
She used to baby-sit my brother Doofy.
她照顾过我弟阿呆
He had the biggest crush on her.
他爱她
It's me, Cind.
是我 辛蒂
Night, Cind.
晚安 辛蒂
(阿呆)
Doofy!
阿呆
Shithead?
那个白痴
- Have you seen Doofy?   - No
- 有看到阿呆吗  - 没有
- Have you seen Doofy?   - No, Sheriff.
- 有看到阿呆吗  - 没有 警长
Has anybody seen Doofy?
有人看到阿呆吗
No.
没有
Yeah. Just went out the back, Sheriff.
他刚从后门走了 警长
No!
不
Shit, son. Yo, what the deal?
妈的 你好吗
Yo, if y'all watchin' this tape right now,
你们如果正在看这部片子
that means I didn't make it.
那表示我没成功
Either I'm a prisoner, or worse, dead.
我不是被关就是 死了
But either way it goes,
不管怎样
I'm gonna tell you all the rules to survive this situation.
我要告诉各位生存法则
Rule number one: You gotta be quick.
第一 动作要快
Rule number two: Don't fall down.
第二 别跌倒
And rule number three: Whatever you do, never look back.
第三 无论如何 都别回头看
Y'all wish me luck.
祝我好运吧
Snatch and run, y'all!
拿了就跑啊
Come back here, you motherfuckers! Son of a bitch!
回来混蛋 痞子
This isn't easy for me.
我知道我们在一起很久了
I know we've been together a long time,
我很难过
but I found somebody else.
但我找到别人了
Okay? I'm in love.
好吗 我有恋人了
Don't look at me like that!
别这样 别那样看着我
We could still be friends.
我们还是朋友
You can come into my room whenever you want.
你可以随时来找我
We just can't... No.
我们就是不行 不
No!
不
Okay, just one time.
好吧 就一次
Yeah. That's it!
好耶 真爽
Whoo! Oh!